kidsgames.biz 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy - Kids Games

**Privacy Policy – kidsgames.biz**   
If you require any more information about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at k-kalyani[a]hotmail.com. The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.kidsgames.biz and how it is used. 

**Cookies –**   
Our site use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.   
**DoubleClick DART Cookie –**   
\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.kidsgames.biz.   
-Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.kidsgames.biz and other sites on the Internet.   
-Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -[ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)   
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.kidsgames.biz send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.kidsgames.biz has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Links to Other Sites –**   
Our website has links to partners and other sites. When you visit another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.   
**Security –**   
We protect personal information against such risks as loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification or destruction, through appropriate security measures.
